Guide to the Gelman Library Assistant University Librarian for Collections records, 1951-1995 RG0108
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1967-2006; RG0108 Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Shelving contract, 1991-2007
    - Telesec, 1994-1996 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Telesec, FY 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Telesec, FY 1998-1999 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Telesec, FY 1999/2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Telesec, FY 2000/2001 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Telesec, FY 2001/2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Telesec, FY 2002/2003 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Telesec, FY 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Telesec, FY 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Telesec, FY 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Telesec, FY 2006-2007 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Short/Title catalog, 1997-2006 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Short/Title catalog: Peck, Linda Levy, 1996-2002 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room, 1982-2006
    - Background materials, 1982-1994 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Collections, 1982-1999 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - IERES support, 1992-1999 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Luce Foundation grant, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Information Center for the Former Soviet Union, etc. - statistics, 1984 August - 1992 December (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Information Center for the Former Soviet Union, etc. - statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Russian Press Services, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Sigur Center, 1992-2002 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Slavic and East European Microfilm Project, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Staffing/personnel, 1992-1995 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Technical services, 1992-2001 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - East Asian Collections, 2002-2005
      - Asian Studies, generally, 2002-2005 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - China Documentation Center [1 of 2], 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - China Documentation Center [2 of 2], 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Japan Resource Center, 2004-2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Taiwan Resource Center, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Space, 1998-2002 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Space 210, 1992-1998 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - SPARC, 1999-2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Special Collections, 1984-2006
    - Background materials, 1997-2004 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Background materials [1 of 2], 1990-2005 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Background materials [2 of 2], 1990-2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Appraisers, 1999-2000 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Bowers, Ann, 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Collections D.C., 1988-1989 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Consultant [1 of 2], 1994-2001 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Consultant [2 of 2], 1994-2001 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/memos, 1985-1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Equipment and software, miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Faculty authors collection, 1993-2000 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts collections inventory, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous donors, 1989-1991 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - National inventory, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Packet for ARL membership application meeting, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Policy and procedures, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Re:Discovery software, 2005 January (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Sales of holdings, 1998-2001 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Africana Research Center 1, 2001-2003
      - Assistant, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Bibliography, 2002-2003 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Brochures and programs, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence and reports, 2001-2002 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Curator, 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Follow-up neede for ARC, 2000-2005 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Africana Research Center 2, 2001-2004
      - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Collection development policy, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Contributions, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Exhibit, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Fundriasing, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Reception announcement, 2002 May (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - W. Lloyd Wright Collection, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Website, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - African American History Site Committee, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Rare Books, 2003
      - Appraisal 1, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Appraisal 2 [1 of 2], 2003 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Appraisal 2 [2 of 2], 2003 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Team SPEC, 1999-2004
      - Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Team development, 2001-2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - University Archives, 1988-1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Records management [1 of 2], 1988-1996 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Records management [2 of 2], 1988-1996 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Preserving GW's history, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Spectra CRC Task force [1 of 3], 2005-2006 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Spectra CRC Task force [2 of 3], 2005-2006 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Spectra CRC Task force [3 of 3], 2005-2006 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Stacks, 1992-2006
    - Background materials, 1988-2005 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Capacity data, 1991-1995 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Periodicals, 1992-2006 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Periodicals storage, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Shift, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Collection move, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Weeding, 1978-2006
      - Background, 1997-1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Criteria, 1978-2001 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - 1989-1994 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - 1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - 1996 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - 2002 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - 2003 December - 2004 January (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - 5th floor weeding, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Staff Management Group, 2005-2006 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Staff Management Group orientation, 2001-2005 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Storage, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Strategic plan, 1987-2006
    - 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 1991-1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 1992-1995 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - [1 of 2], 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - [2 of 2], 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - [1 of 2], 1995-1998 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - [2 of 2], 1995-1998 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - [1 of 2], 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - [2 of 2], 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 1999-2002 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - [1 of 2], 2000-2003 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - [2 of 2], 2000-2003 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - [1 of 2], 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - [2 of 2], 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2006 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - 2004-2007 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 2005-2008 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 2006-2009 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Strategic Planning, 1987-2006
      - AUL vision statements, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Background materials, 1994-2001 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Strategic Planning Group, 1996-2006
        - Background materials, 1996-1998 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - Retreat [1 of 2], 2006 January (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - Retreat [2 of 2], 2006 January (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Processes, values, etc., 1984-2000 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Student code, 1999-2006 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Subject specialists, 1989-1998
    - Background materials, 1989-1992 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Definition and mission, 1984-1998 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Performance expectations, 1994-1998 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Surveys [1 of 2], 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Surveys [2 of 2], 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Systems Operating Group (SOG), 1986 January 14 - August 22 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Tattletaping project, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Telecommuting, 1996-1998 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Temp services, 1998-2006 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Theses, 1979-2006
    - General, 1982-2001 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Electronic theses and dissertations, 2001-2006 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Gelman processing/cataloging, 1979-2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Title VI, 1994-2006
    - Applications [1 of 2], 1994-1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Applications [2 of 2], 1994-1999 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Expanding grant funds, 1999-2005 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Latin American Studies, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - President Stephen Joel Trachtenburg. Remarks to the George Washington University Assembly, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Trimester proposal, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - UCITA, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - University, 1988-2006
    - Background materials [1 of 2], 1988-2006 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Background materials [2 of 2], 1988-2006 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Academic productivity (GWU reports), undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Compliance, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Enrollment, 2004-2006 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Policies, 1995-2002 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - UMI microfilm project, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - UMI Proquest usage reports, 1994 September 14 - November 16 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Campus, 1990-2006
    - Background [1 of 2], 1990-2004 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Background [2 of 2], 1990-2004 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Crash Analysis Center, 1992-1994 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Campus Library, 1994-2006
    - Background, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Background, 2002-2005 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Budget [1 of 2], 1990-2006 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Budget [2 of 2], 1990-2006 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Collection development, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Electronic library, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Orders, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Voyager [1 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Voyager [2 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Voyager [3 of 3], 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Voyager for collection development, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Washington Research Library Alliance, 1984-1986
    - Background, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/memos, 1985-1986 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Central Depository Facility, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium, 1986-2006
    - General [1 of 2], 1992-2005 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - General [2 of 2], 1992-2005 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Administration, 1989-2004 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Final report of the collaborative CAP Project, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Library Directors's meetings [1 of 3], 1998-2006 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Library Directors's meetings [2 of 3], 1998-2006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Library Directors's meetings [3 of 3], 1998-2006 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1997-2006 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Cataloging, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Digitization projects, 2001-2002 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Guides, 1989-2003 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Metalib, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1988-1995 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Off-site storage, 1986-2006
      - General, 1986-2004 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Charges, 1994-2006 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Lisner to WRLC, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Protected serials titles [1 of 3], 1994-1998 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Protected serials titles [2 of 3], 1994-1998 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Protected serials titles [3 of 3], 1994-1998 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Protected serials titles, 1997 September (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Statistics [1 of 3], 1990-2004 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Statistics [2 of 3], 1990-2004 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Statistics [3 of 3], 1990-2004 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - System [1 of 2], 1997 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - System [2 of 2], 1997 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Committees, 1997-2006
      - Access Services Committee, 1997-2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Collection Development Advisory Committee, 1984-2002
        - General, 1984-2006 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Joint approval plan, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Protected titles, 1990-2002 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Protected serials titles policy statement, 1992-2000 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Protected serials titles - physics, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - WLN Conspectus, 1993-1997 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Digital Library Advisory Committee, 1995-2001 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Workflow, 1997-2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Workshops and seminars - software, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Yankee Book Peddler [1 of 2], 2001-2004 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Yankee Book Peddler [2 of 2], 2001-2004 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Allocations Task Force files, 2000-2005; RG0108 Series 3 (Box UP0001)
  - Allocation Task Force, 2002-2006 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Allocation Task Force: meetings, etc., 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Allocation Task Force: background, 1998-2002 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Allocation Task Force report, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Allocations Committee [1 of 2], 2000 - 2001 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Allocations Committee [2 of 2], 2000 - 2001 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Allocations literature review, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Collections Spreadsheet Task Force, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Allocations formula FY2003, 2002 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Allocation formula, 2002 - 2003 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Allocation Task Force data sources, 2004 - 2005 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Allocations Task Force, FY2005, 2004 - 2005 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Allocations Task Force circulation statistics, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - FY 07: circulation, 2007-2008 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - FY 07: Area Studies, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - FY 08: circulation, 2007-2008 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - FY 07: credit hours, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - FY 07: credit hours, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Data sources FY 07, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - FY 07: e-journal usage statistics, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - FY 07: faculty, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - FY 07: journal publishing universe, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - FY 08: journal publishing universe, 2007-2008 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - FY 07: monographic publishing universe, 2006-2007 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - FY 08: monographic publishing universe, 2007-2008 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - FY 08, 2007-2008 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Construction project files, 1984-2010; RG0108 Series 4; 1.75 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains blueprints dated 1984-94. These blueprints document the library renovations to the 1st, 2nd, 3rd, 6th and 7th floors. Formerly ACC#680
  It also contains information on the construction of NSA and the International Brotherhood of Teamsters room on the 7th floor of the library.
  - Gelman Library 3rd floor renovations, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Gelman Library blueprints, RG0108 Subseries 4.1 (Map-folder 1)
    - Gelman Library - Renovations, 06/1985
    - Gelman Library - Floor plans, 06/1991
    - Gelman Library - 1st and 3rd Floor Renovations, 06/1986
    - Gelman Library - 2nd Floor Renovations, 12/1984
    - Gelman Library - 6th Floor Renovations, 10/1992
    - Gelman Library - 7th Floor Renovations, 03/1994-05/1994
  - National Security Archive blueprints, 1995; RG0108 Series 4.2; 0.25 Linear feet (Map-folder 2)
    This series contains blueprints. These are dated 1995 and are blueprints of the National Security Archive in Gelman Library.
    Formerly ACC#686
    - National Security Archive in the Gelman Libary blueprints, 1995
  - IBT and NSA Room Construction, 2009-2010; RG0108 Series 4.3; 1.50 Linear Feet 3 manuscript boxes
    - NSA construction, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - IBT Donations monetary, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - IBT meeting minutes, agenda, 2010-2011 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - IBT promotional materials, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - IBT research center visitors talking points, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - IBT proposal and construction, September 2008-March 2011 (Box 83, Folder 7-24)
    - Teamsters Advisory Board, 2011-2012 (Box 83, Folder 25-26)
    - IBT Research Center Opening Event, 2009-2010 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - IBT opening event, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - IBT Room - RFI Logs, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - IBT Room - Architectural specifications, November-December 2009 (Box 84, Folder 2-4)
    - IBT Room - operations and maintenance manual, June 2010 (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
    - IBT Room - Room specifications, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
- Statistics, 1997; RG0108 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains one video cassette. The video is an interview with Sam Greenhouse about statistics.
  Formerly ACC#663
  - Statistics Interview: A conversation with Sam Greenhouse, 1997 August 8 (Box SHARED Box 5)
    General note
    56min. - ASA Distinguished Statistician Videotape Series
- WLN Conspectus files, 1994 - 2003; 1998-2001; RG0108 Series 6
  - WLN conspectus [1 of 5], 1998 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - WLN conspectus [2 of 5], 1998 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - WLN conspectus [3 of 5], 1998 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - WLN conspectus [4 of 5], 1998 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - WLN conspectus [5 of 5], 1998 - 2000 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - WLN conspectus reports, 2001 - 2003 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - WLN conspectus users guide, vers. 7.1, 1999 August (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - WLN conspectus software user's manual, ver. 6.3, 1996 January (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium workshop: using the WLN conspectus, 1998 June 8 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - WLN conspectus proof reports, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - WLN conspectus overlapping areas, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Collection assessment at Gelman Library: subject specialist meeting, 1998 December 14 - 15 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Using the conspectus method: a collection assessment handbook, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - WLN Conspectus promotional materials [1 of 2], 1994 - 2000 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - WLN Conspectus promotional materials [1 of 2], 1994 - 2000 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Workflow Implementation Team project files, 2002 - 2003; RG0108 Series 7
  - WIT [1 of 2], 2001-2004 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - WIT [2 of 2], 2001-2004 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - WIT, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - WIT [1 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - WIT [2 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Book import profiles, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Caroline C. Long's notes, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Contract with R2, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Fund codes, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Implementation schedule charts, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Jean Pec and quality control at BBS, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - New titles received lists, 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Organization charts, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Procedures sent to R2, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - R2 and Caroline C. Long observations, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - R2 notebooks - table contents, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Schedules - meetings with R2, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Smithsonian staff visit, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Staff memos, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Staff presentations - new workflows, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Travel, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Workflow Implementation Team minutes, key measures, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder [1 of 3], 2002 April - 2003 March (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder [2 of 3], 2002 April - 2003 March (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder [3 of 3], 2002 April - 2003 March (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder [1 of 2], 2003 March - 2003 June (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder [2 of 2], 2003 March - 2003 June (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder, 2003 June - August (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Workflow Implementation Team binder, 2003 August - 2003 October (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Workflow Implementation Team approvals, gifts binder, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Workflow Implementation Team BBS slips binder [1 of 2], 2002 June - 2003 April (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Workflow Implementation Team BBS slips binder [2 of 2], 2002 June - 2003 April (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Workflow Implementation Team miscellaneous binder [1 of 2], 2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Workflow Implementation Team miscellaneous binder [2 of 2], 2002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [1 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Contains miscellaneous materials filed in the front pocket of the original binder.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [2 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Contains materials related to implementation, future workflows, and agendas and minutes.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [3 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Contains agendas and minutes.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [4 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    Contains agenda and minutes.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [5 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    Contains agenda and minutes, team task documentation, staff information, and workflow change alerts.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [6 of 6], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Contains workflow change alerts, vendor information, and background information.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [1 of 5], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    Contains information on team tasks and workflow change alerts.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [2 of 5], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    Contains workflow change alerts and ladder charts.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [3 of 5], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    Contains vendor information.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [4 of 5], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    Contain background information.
  - Workflow Implementation Taskforce binder [5 of 5], 2002 - 2003 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    Contains information on key measures.
- Ad Hoc Committee on Publications file, 1951-1989; RG0108 Series 8; 0.25 Linear Feet 1 folder (Box 82)